+91 87927 53090 | nagendra.prajwal@outlook.com | LinkedIn | Bangalore, KA, IN - 560 062

About me

Having around 6+ years of experience in web development, I've worked on various technologies like Angular, React, Flutter, ASP.NET MVC, WPF, and Silverlight. Although started as full-stack developer, I prefer to be a front-end developer, as I had always focused on *cleaner*, *easy-to-use interfaces* which makes our user's journey a happy one.

Work Experience

SOFTWARE ENGINEER III; F5, INC; BANGALORE, INDIA – 2020-PRESENT

Worked on VoltConsole platform SaaS division and also on brand website, documentation portals etc. Majorly used Angular and React (Gatsby) for front-end development.

SENIOR SOFTWARE ENGINEER; VOTERCIRCLE, INC.; BANGALORE, INDIA – 2019-2020

Worked on developing OutreachCircle platform, which is an entirely new, research-based approach of connecting with voters by utilising the supporter's personal contact book. Here, we are using Angular, React, Flutter, NextJS for various apps along with GraqhQL.

SENIOR SYSTEMS ENGINEER; INFOSYS LTD.; BANGALORE, INDIA - 2018-2019

Worked primarily on CPQ solution for an Agro-Tech company, based on Configlt. I was taking care of front-end app, which has to be used by dealers, customers, and guest users on desktop-web, mobile-web, and mobile-app. Tech stack used was Angular, React, .net Core, SAP Hybris, and related SAP products.

SYSTEMS ENGINEER; INFOSYS LTD.; BANGALORE, INDIA - 2016-2018

Worked primarily on analytical tool for a leading Aerospace company. Initially started as Silverlight project in fall of 2009, when I joined, it was overdue for an overhaul. Entire presentation layer was re-written using ASP.NET MVC, jQuery, and Bootstrap in the span of 8 months.

Education

Visvesvaraya Technological University – *Bachelor of Engineering*, Passed with first class (70.01%), 2015

Top Skills

TypeScript, JavaScript, React, Angular, CSS3, Sass, Webpack, C#, ASP.NET MVC, WPF.

Certifications and Accreditations

- Microsoft Certified Solutions Developer App Builder, 2017.
 - Microsoft Certified Solutions Associate Web Applications, 2017.
 - HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and ASP.NET MVC (exams: 70 480, 70 486).
- AWS Technical Professional (2015 2017), Partner Accreditation Programme.

For detailed profile

- LinkedIn: https://linkedin.com/in/nagendraprajwal
- StackOverflow: https://stackoverflow.com/story/nagendra.prajwal